youthmasti.com 2015-12-19

# Media3K Privacy Policy | Media3K | Its All About Media

This Privacy Policy describes how Media3K.com and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use Media3K.com services.

#### Your Video Content

Media3K.com is a best effort service to automatically process your content to the specifications that you enter into our system. In most cases, your material is not viewed as it passes automatically through Media3K.com systems, however by using Media3K.com you agree that Media3K.com staff may view your content for the purposes of quality control of our systems and processes, within the terms of our privacy policy.

Media3K.com make best efforts to upload your processed video content to video hosting sites that you ask us to. By using Media3K.com you agree that Media3K.com and its employees have no control over the privacy of video content past when it is uploaded to third parties on your behalf. You also agree that Media3K cannot in most cases take down or take back video materials posted to video hosting sites on your behalf. You agree that you must work directly with your video hosting site to take down or modify video content or modify the manner in which it is privately or publicly displayed.

#### Personal Information

Non-Account Activity. You can watch Media3K videos on Media3K without having a Media3K Account. You can also contact us about a particular Media3K video without having a Media3K Account.

Account-Related Activity. Certain other activities on Media3K—like uploading content, posting comments—require you to have a Media3K Account. We ask for some personal information when you create a Media3K Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Media3K Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.

Usage Information. We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Media3K, the contacts you communicate with, the Media3K videos you watch, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in Media3K (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. “Web Beacons”) in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

Content Uploaded to Site. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

#### Uses

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Media3K Sites, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Media3K Sites, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.

Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload content or send messages through the Media3K Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Media3K Site changes or for customer service purposes).

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Media3K Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Media3K Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

#### Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Media3K Sites, in which case you can still view Media3K videos and explore the Media3K Sites, but Media3K may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some advanced Media3K features may, for authentication purposes, require you to sign up for other Media3K services. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your Account page.

#### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Media3K allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Media3K Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Media3K Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Media3K does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Media3K to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Media3K Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Media3K’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
